

PROFILE

Hi my name is Arturo Alvarez and I'm a web developer, I started my career by learning code by myself, and since I began to learn I have worked on many personal projects and also as a freelance for startups here in my country, I have a great enthusiasm for work with great companies worldwide and to learn their professional practices to become a better developer, so I hope that we can work together on many projects.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+52 55-8167-9527

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/arturo-alvarez-martinez-ab9b77151/

GITHUB:

https://github.com/Artufelii/

CORREO:

artufelii@gmail.com

ARTURO ALVAREZ

WORK EXPERIENCE

Back-end web Developer

FRAGMODS, Ecatepec de Morelos, México.

August 2022 - present

- Designed and built user-facing web applications using React
- Developed RESTful APIs using Node.js and Express
- Utilized MongoDB for data storage and management
- Implemented authentication and authorization using jsonwebtoken.

Front-end web developer

FRAGMODS, Ecatepec de Morelos, México.

January 2019 – August 2022

- Created responsive websites using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Worked with team members to develop website features
- Debugged code and resolved issues
- Implemented design changes based on feedback
- Wrote code to meet project specifications

EDUCATION

08/2017 - 12/2022 CIUDAD DE MEXICO, MEXICO

Ingeneria en Robotica Industrial | Engineer Instituto Politecnico Nacional

SKILLS

- React js
- Node is
- Mongo DB
- Tailwind css